So this lovely person, Panamamasita, said, girl, I'm so glad you came back to IG to give us
instructions. Life and face, life and face, life and face, life and face. Hope they are being nicer
this time. And I said, lolololol they are. I attract a much higher IQ these days. But you know
what? Upon further review, I think what it really is, is that the people that I attract now are more
so interested in learning and information, in sharing information than on whether or not they
like me. Because I noticed this whenever I do like interviews with gossip bloggers or entertainment
like pop culture pages, the conversation a lot of times is not on what I'm actually discussing or
what they have gleaned or how they've been inspired or if they disagree on what I'm actually saying.
It always ends up being just about like, I like her, I don't like her. And I think that's a really
bigger conversation around why we're not able to see mobilization and organizing on the level that
we need to in this nation. And it's about the celebrity culture. It's about the surface. It's
about the optics. It's about people being so much more caught up in how they are feeling about somebody
that has nothing to do with their life than how they are actually feeling in regards to the decisions
being made about their lives. And I feel like people are far more apt to just like somebody or
not like somebody versus actually look into their actions. And when we see that on like a entertainer
level, that's one thing. But on a politician, like lawmaker level, that's incredibly important.
Hmm. I'm not saying anything new. This has been going on for quite some time, but we're at a crisis
level with this. So anywho, moral of the story is everything I just said. And also it don't matter
if you like me or not. It don't matter. It don't matter. It don't matter. It don't matter. It don't
matter. It don't matter. It don't matter. It don't matter. Because it's really, it's not going to
change my life. And more importantly, it's not going to change yours. And whether you like me or
not, if you like this sweatshirt, you can get your own at my little shop, amandalandexports.com.
So, let's see.